<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Extra Credit on FortiGate CNF Workshop</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/5_modulefive.html</link><description>Recent content in Extra Credit on FortiGate CNF Workshop</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/5_modulefive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Task 1: Deploying CNF Instances and GWLBe endpoints</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/5_modulefive/51_task1.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/5_modulefive/51_task1.html</guid><description>Task 1: Deploying CNF Instances and GWLBe endpoints Note For this section of the workshop we will be using the us-west-1 (N. California) region. There is a deployment of another Application VPC where FortiGate-CNF will inspect the ingress &amp;amp; egress traffic flows. Also there is a Management VPC where FortiAnalyzer, FortiManager, and a Nikto Scanner are deployed.
In the AWS CloudFormation console, make sure you are in the us-west-1 (N. California) region, then toggle the view nested button to off &amp;gt; then select the stack name &amp;gt; and on the details pane select the outputs tab.</description></item><item><title>Task 2: FortiManager Integration</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/5_modulefive/52_task2.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/5_modulefive/52_task2.html</guid><description>Task 2: FortiManager Integration In the AWS CloudFormation console, make sure you are in the us-west-1 (N. California) region, then toggle the view nested button to off &amp;gt; then select the stack name &amp;gt; and on the details pane select the outputs tab. You should see the output for FortiManagerLoginURL. Login to the FortiManager with the username admin and the password FORTInet123!. In the FortiManager GUI for the first login, you will be prompted to complete the setup wizard.</description></item><item><title>Task 3: FortiAnalyzer Integration</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/5_modulefive/53_task3.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/5_modulefive/53_task3.html</guid><description>Task 2: FortiAnalyzer Integration In the AWS CloudFormation console, make sure you are in the us-west-1 (N. California) region, then toggle the view nested button to off &amp;gt; then select the stack name &amp;gt; and on the details pane select the outputs tab. You should see the output for FortiAnalyzerLoginURL. Login to the FortiAnalyzer with the username admin and the password FORTInet123!. In the FortiAnalyzer GUI for the first login, you will be prompted to complete the setup wizard.</description></item></channel></rss>