<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Secure AWS workloads with FortiGate CNF SaaS on FortiGate CNF Workshop</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Secure AWS workloads with FortiGate CNF SaaS on FortiGate CNF Workshop</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/1_moduleone.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/1_moduleone.html</guid><description>Secure AWS workloads with FortiGate CNF SaaS Welcome! AWS Software-Defined Networking (SDN) is elastic, complex, and quite different than traditional on-premise networking. In this workshop you will learn how to use FortiGate Cloud Native Firewall as a Service (FortiGate CNF) to protect your AWS workloads deployed in common architecture patterns.
This workshop is intended to help accomplish the following:
Learn common AWS networking concepts such as routing traffic in and out of VPCs for various traffic flows Interact with FortiGate CNF Portal to deploy CNF instances, build security policy sets, and deploy them Test traffic flows in an example environment and use FortiGate CNF to control traffic flows Learning Objectives At the end of this workshop, you will complete the following objectives:</description></item><item><title>Workshop Prerequisites</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/2_moduletwo.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/2_moduletwo.html</guid><description>Workshop Prerequisites In this section we will step through the what is needed before you can get the most out of the rest of the workshop!</description></item><item><title>Workshop Hands On</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/3_modulethree.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/3_modulethree.html</guid><description>Workshop Hands On</description></item><item><title>Workshop Test Traffic</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/4_modulefour.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/4_modulefour.html</guid><description>In this section you will validate that the policy set is controlling traffic as intended. Below is the overall architecture of the environment.
We will look into these specific traffic flows:
Distributed Ingress Distributed Egress Centralized Egress Centralized East West</description></item><item><title>Extra Credit</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/5_modulefive.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/5_modulefive.html</guid><description>This is an extra credit section that gives you hands on with using FortiManager and FortiAnalyzer with FortiGate-CNF.
This will give you another environment to do the following:
Add a CNF Instance to FMG Import the base &amp;lsquo;allow all&amp;rsquo; policy set Modify the policy set to apply L7 controls including SSL MitM Install this to a CNF Instance Add a CNF Instance to FortiAnalyzer Inspect drill down widgets in FortiView Inspect formatted logs in Log View Tip If you are short on time, we recommend scrolling through the section to see how easy it is to accomplish the tasks above and enjoy the results!</description></item><item><title>Providing Feedback</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/6_modulesix.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/FortiCNF/6_modulesix.html</guid><description>Thank You! Providing Feedback Tip We truly appreciate your time and efforts to review FortiGate CNF and value your feedback greatly. You will receive a request to complete a post event survey and can get a gift if you complete it while on site!</description></item></channel></rss>